莉娜。
Leena.
你以前没有回答我。
You didn't a-- answer me before.
你父母在这里工作吗？
Do your parents work here?
你为什么这么想？
Why would you think that?
因为你，我是什么？
Because you're--I'm what?
丽娜？
Leena?
放下它。
Put it down.
莉娜，把它放下，现在。
Leena, put it down, now.
你没告诉我她是个孩子。
You didn't tell me she was a child.
那是因为她不是。
That's because she's not.
莉娜患有腺体疾病
Leena suffers from a gland disorder
这导致了比例侏儒症，
which causes, uh, proportional dwarfism,
实际上，她在10岁左右就停止了生长。
essentially halting her growth around age ten.
别搞错了。
Make no mistake.
莉娜看起来像个孩子，但她是个成年女人。
Leena may look like a child, but she is a grown woman.
准确地说是三十一。
Thirty one, to be exact.
当莉娜第一次到达时，
When Leena first arrived,
她拼命挣脱束缚
she struggled so hard against her restraints
她会流血不止。
that she would bleed severely.
这对我们所有人都是一个教训
It was a lesson for all of us
在她自由意志的深处。
on the depths of her will to be free.
丽娜早年的大部分生活
Much of Leena's early life
为了生存，她尽了一切努力。
was spent doing whatever she could to survive.
但她从未变老，至少在外表上没有。
But she never grew older, at least not on the outside.
想象一下你的一生，
Imagine going through your whole life,
世界只看到一个孩子。
the world seeing only a child.
非常重要的是，你不要那样看待她。
It is very important that you do not see her in that way.
莉娜尽可能多地利用她的痛苦。
Leena uses her affliction as much as she suffers from it.
她是个出色的骗子。
She's a exceptional con artist.
两年前，莉娜慢慢地走了过来
Two years ago, Leena wormed her way
通过伪装成逃跑者进入这个家庭。
into this family by posing as a runaway.
这个家庭收留了她。他们喂她。他们给她穿上衣服。
This family took her in. They fed her. They clothed her.
通常，莉娜会尽可能地偷东西
Normally, Leena would simply steal whatever she could
然后消失，但这次，
and then disappear, but this time,
她，嗯。。。
she, um...
好吧，让我这样说。
Well, let me put it this way.
她现在住在这里。
She lives here now.
Idti。
Idti.
艾迪！
Idti!
她是这样做的。
She does that.
我们还有多久，爸爸？
How much longer have we got, Daddy?
我们还有两分钟亲爱的。
We have two minutes, darling.
你在用心学习我，小萨拉。
You're learning me by heart, little Sara.
不，爸爸。我对你了如指掌。你在我心里。
No, Daddy. I know you by heart. You're inside my heart.
我们会勇敢的，不是吗？
We're gonna be brave, aren't we?
是的，爸爸。
Yes, Daddy.
是的，爸爸。莉娜：你好，德米特里。
Yes, Daddy.LEENA: Hello, Dmitri.
你准时到了。
You're on time.
太完美了。
It's perfect.
我不能自己绑这些。
I can't tie these myself.
我想为你做点好事。
I want to do something nice for you.
你可以进来。
You can come in.
是 啊是 啊
Yeah. Yeah.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我爸爸得走了。他几乎每天都会回来。
My daddy has to go away. He'll return most any day.
我做不到。
I can't do it.
我现在可以做了。
I can do it now.
我随时都可能看到我爸爸回到我身边。
Any moment I may see my daddy coming back to me.
我爸爸得走了。
My daddy has to go away.
伊迪，你想要一些糖果吗？
Idti, do you want some candy?
艾迪！
Idti!
她切断了饲料。
She cut the feed.
我很抱歉，安娜。
I'm so sorry, Anna.
希望警方能找到她
Hopefully, the police will find her
在其他人受伤之前。
before anyone else is hurt.
我敢肯定，这不是我们希望的开始。
Not quite the start we had hoped for, I'm sure.
这工作不适合我。
This job isn't for me.
哦，安娜。
Oh, Anna.
通常只需要一个。
It usually takes only one.
嗯？
Huh?
不要害怕。我是警察。
Don't be frightened. I am police.
呃，你父母在哪里？
Uh, where are your parents?
我父母在美国。
My parents are in America.
甜心，你叫什么名字？
Sw-- sweetheart, what is your name?
我叫埃丝特。
My name is Esther.
♪ 跟我来
♪ Coming with me
♪ 通过衰老，恐惧，冲突♪
♪ Through the aging The fearing, the strife ♪
♪ 是包裹上的微笑♪
♪ It's the smiling On the package ♪
♪ 是沙子里的脸♪
♪ It's the faces in the sand ♪
♪ 是这个想法让你向上移动♪
♪ It's the thought That moves you upwards ♪
♪ 用双手拥抱我♪
♪ Embracing me with two hands ♪
♪ 右边会带你去一些地方是的，也许会去海滩♪
♪ Right will take you places Yeah, maybe to the beach ♪
♪ 当你的朋友来的时候，他们会哭♪
♪ When your friends They do come crying ♪
♪ 现在告诉他们你的荣幸已经定了♪
♪ Tell 'em Now your pleasure's set ♪
♪ 缓慢释放时♪
♪ Upon slow release ♪
♪ 嘿，等等
♪ Hey, wait
栅栏
Fence!
♪ 对命运敏感，而不是。。。
♪ Sensitive to fate, not...
♪ 很久以前
♪ The long way back
是 啊
Yeah!
♪ 桑迪，为什么我们不能换个角度看？♪
♪ Sandy, why can't we Look the other way? ♪
杀了它。甘纳：谢谢，伙计。
Killed it.GUNNAR: Thanks, man.
我真为你骄傲亲爱的。嗯，是的。
I'm so proud of you, sweetheart.Mm-hmm, yeah.
干得好伙计谢谢各位。
Great job, pal.Thanks, guys.
你认为你会呆多久？
How long do you think you'll be?
事实上，今晚有一群人在一起。
Actually, a bunch of people are getting together tonight.
恭喜你。
Well, congrats.
我会在家里等你们。
I'll, uh, see you guys back at the house.
我是说，这应该是家庭之夜。
I mean, this was supposed to be family night.
什么，他不应该和朋友们一起玩吗？
What, is he not supposed to have fun with his friends?
哦，天哪。他所做的就是玩得开心。
Oh, God. All he does is have fun.
不，甘纳工作得很辛苦。
No, Gunnar works his tail off.
当他不学习的时候，他在击剑。
When he's not studying, he's fencing.
他过着自己的生活。
He's living his life.
不要那样做。不要进入你的头脑。
Don't do that. Don't go into your head.
我需要你在场。甘纳需要你。
I need you to be present. Gunnar needs you.
哦，对不起。我没有参加那场比赛吗？
Oh, sorry. Was I not at that match?
埃丝特不会回来了，艾伦。
Esther's not coming back, Allen.
我也想念她。我愿意。
I miss her too. I do.
每天的每一刻。
Every moment of every day.
他在这里干什么？
What is he doing here?
你好，艾伦。
Hello, Allen.
我们有你女儿埃丝特的最新消息。
We have an update on your daughter Esther.
从埃丝特那里得到的一点点，
From the little we've gotten from Esther,
我们相信是一个女人绑架了她，把她带到了俄罗斯
we believe a woman abducted her, brought her to Russia
把她当成自己的孩子
and passed her off as her own child
直到埃丝特设法逃跑。
until Esther managed to escape.
我们还没有得到很多细节。
We haven't gotten many specifics yet.
也许当她觉得安全的时候，
Perhaps when she's feeling safer,
她可以对她所经历的事情有更多的了解。
she can shed some more light on what she's been through.
我们有一位儿童治疗师，她将与之合作。
We have a child therapist that she'll be working with.
好的
Good.
她现在需要的是她的家人。
What she needs right now is her family.
为变化做好准备。
Be prepared for changes.
四年是孩子成长的很长时间。
Four years is a long time in the development of a child.
埃丝特？
Esther?
亲爱的，是我。
Sweetheart, it's me.
是妈妈。
It's Mommy.
我能看见你吗？
Can I-- can I see you?
亲爱的，这是--
Sweetie, it's--
是妈妈。
it's Mommy.
我以为我再也见不到你了。
I thought I would never see you again.
现在一切都好了。
Everything is right, now.
你很久没见到我们了。
It's been so long since you've seen any of us.
让我们看看我能不能——哦，爸爸来了。
Let's see if I can-- Oh, there's Daddy.
这是我们的慈善活动之一。
This was one of our charity events.
那天晚上他看起来很帅，不是吗？
He looked so handsome that night, didn't he?
空姐：我能给你拿点别的吗？
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Can I grab you anything else?
不，谢谢。
No, thanks.
哦，说到魔鬼。
Oh, speak of the devil.
你哥哥可能比你记得的高一英尺。
Your brother is probably a foot taller than you would remember.
哦，有一个Mup Mup。她对我们很好。
Oh, there's Mup-Mup. She's been so good to us.
哦，我等不及要见她了。
Oh, I can't wait to see her.
不，亲爱的。
No, sweetie.
她过去了。回想起现在只有我们四个人了。
She passed. Remember? It's just the four of us now.
我得上厕所。
I have to use the restroom.
呃，洗手间在那边吗？
Uh, is the restroom over there?
不，就在那边。
No, it's just right back over there.
在后面？哦，嗯。
Over in the back? Oh.Mm-hmm.
非常感谢。服务员：不客气。
Thank you.ATTENDANT: You're welcome.
“迫不及待地想见到她。”太蠢了。
"Can't wait to see her." So stupid.
哦，爸爸和甘纳就在楼下。
Oh, Daddy and Gunnar are just downstairs.
你认为父亲会认出我吗？
Do you think Father will recognize me?
呃，如果你一直叫他“父亲”，也许不会
Uh, maybe not if you keep calling him "father."
爸爸崔西亚：是的，这样更好。
Dad. TRICIA: Yeah, that's better.
在这里让我看看你。
Here. Let me look at you.
哦，天哪。你看起来。。。
Oh, my God. You look...
像个小姑娘。你已经长大了很多。
like a little lady. You've grown up so much.
把这个脱下来。
Take this off.
这样更好。它不那么严肃。
That's better. It's less austere.
这是--
This is--
很抱歉不，对不起。我--
Sorry.No, I-- I'm sorry. I--
来吧，我们走吧。
Come on. Let's go.
我想我很紧张。
I think I'm nervous.
好吧，这是一大步。
All right, big step.
爸爸？
Daddy?
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
不敢相信真的是你。
Can't believe it's really you.
我一直都知道。我一直都知道。
I always knew. I always knew.
你好，甘纳。
Hello, Gunnar.
嘿
Hey.
我想我们可以做得比“嘿”好一点
I think we could do a little bit better than, "Hey."
你不这么认为吗？艾伦：来吧。
Don't you think?ALLEN: Come.
很高兴你回来了。
Glad you're back.
我也是。
Me, too.
我们回家怎么样？莉娜：是的。
How about we go home, huh?LEENA: Yes.
我们回家吧。
Let's go home.
欢迎回家，埃丝特。
Welcome home, Esther.
我们就这样离开了。
We left it just as it was.
我们一直都知道你会回家的。
We always knew you would come back home.
隐马尔可夫模型。
Hmm.
我的意思是，你可能已经长大了很多，
I mean, you've probably outgrown so much,
但是我们有很多圣诞节和生日
but we have a lot of Christmases and birthdays
为了弥补，
to make up for,
让我们知道你在干什么，
so just let us know what you're into,
你可能会得到它。
and you might get it.
我喜欢画画。你喜欢画画吗？
I like painting.You like to paint?
你以前从未对绘画感兴趣。
You were never interested in painting before.
也许你们两个
Well, maybe you two
可以花一些时间在你的工作室。
can spend some time in your studio.
没有什么能让我更快乐。
Nothing would make me happier.
所以，嗯，计划是，
So, um, plan is,
明天你要和西格医生谈谈。
tomorrow you're gonna talk to Dr. Segar.
你还记得她吗？
Do you remember her?
她有只鹦鹉叫悉尼。
She had the parrot named Sydney.Mm-hmm.
可以
Okay.
如果你需要什么。。。
Well, if you need anything...
我们就在大厅下面，好吗？
We're right down the hall, all right?
♪ 让你可怜的心破碎一点♪
♪ And let your poor heart Break a little ♪
♪ 这就是
♪ That's the story of
♪ 这就是爱的荣耀♪
♪ That's the glory of love ♪
♪ 你得笑一笑
♪ You gotta laugh a little
♪ 哭一点♪
♪ Cry a little ♪
♪ 在云层翻滚之前♪
♪ Before the clouds Roll by a little ♪
♪ 这就是爱的故事，这是爱的荣耀♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
接待员：好的，你可以进去了。
RECEPTIONIST: Okay, you can go in.
西格医生马上就来。
Dr. Segar will be right with you.
塞格医生：几分钟后我就要见到她了。
DR. SEGAR: I'm seeing her in a few minutes.
我觉得你现在介入还为时过早警探。
I think it's too soon for you to get involved, Detective.
我想先和她单独谈谈。
I'd like to talk to her alone first.
听着，我得走了。
Look, I have to go.
西格尔博士：你不知道
DR. SEGAR: You have no idea
见到你我真高兴埃丝特。
how happy I am to see you, Esther.
欢迎回家。
Welcome home.
好吧，现在，你肯定不是我曾经认识的那个小女孩了。
Well, now, you're certainly not the little girl I once knew.
你现在是个年轻女士了。
You're a young lady now.
你还记得我告诉你的吗
Do you remember what I told you
我们第一次开会是什么时候？
when we first began our sessions?
我告诉过你如果我问任何问题
I told you if I ask any questions
那会让你不舒服，我们会停下来。
that make you uncomfortable, we'll stop.
我希望我的父母像你一样。
I wish my parents were like you.
为什么呢
How so?
他们一直问我发生了什么，
They keep asking what happened to me,
但我还没准备好告诉他们。
but I'm not ready to tell them about it.
塞格医生：那很好。
DR. SEGAR: And that's perfectly fine.
我希望你能跟我谈谈，
I am hoping you'll talk to me about it,
但只有当你准备好了，好吗？
but only when you're ready, okay?
话虽如此，
Having said that,
你有什么要告诉我的吗
is there anything you want to tell me
关于你离开的时间？
about your time away?
你想玩吗，悉尼？
You want to play, Sydney?
我想悉尼想和我一起玩。
I think Sydney wants to play with me.
你好，我记得你。
Hello, I remember you.
你还记得我吗？
You remember me?
塞格医生：轮到你了。埃丝特，你可以在外面等。
DR. SEGAR: Your turn. Esther, you can wait out here.
我只是想和你妈妈谈谈。
I'm just going to need to talk to your mom for a moment.
你好，你好。
Hello.Hi.
我喜欢你的耳环。
I like your earrings.
哦，谢谢你，亲爱的。
Oh, thank you, honey.
你在写什么？哦，对不起。我很抱歉。
What are you writing? Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
没关系。莉娜：对不起。
It's okay.LEENA: I'm sorry.
让我去把这个弄干净。
Let me go get this cleaned up.
SEGAR医生：她看起来和你记得的一样？
DR. SEGAR: She seem the same as you remember?
不同的
Different?
她当然不一样了。
Well, of course she's different.
塞格医生：她现在有口音了。
DR. SEGAR: She has an accent now.
考虑到她去过哪里，这不寻常吗？
Is that unusual, considering where she's been?
塞格博士：不一定。
DR. SEGAR: Not necessarily.
她演讲时在那儿呆了很长时间
She was there a long time when her speech
仍在发展中。
was still developing.
但我要告诉你，她的身体状况要好得多
But I will tell you, she is in far better shape
在智力和情感上都比我预期的要高。
intellectually and emotionally than I would expect.
那很好，对吧？
Well, that's good, right?
塞格博士：我确实注意到了一些不一致之处。
DR. SEGAR: I did notice some inconsistencies.
例如，她说那是悉尼。
For example, she said that was Sydney.
悉尼是一只金刚鹦鹉。
Sydney was a macaw.
明亮的橙色和四倍的大小。
Bright orange and four times the size.
然而，今天，她把这只鸟叫做悉尼
Yet, today, she addressed this bird as Sydney
满怀信心。崔西亚：你在说什么？
with complete confidence.TRICIA: What are you getting at?
西格尔博士：对我来说，这就像一场表演。
DR. SEGAR: To me, it felt like a performance.
他打了我，撕破了我的衣服！
He hit me and ripped my dress!
我想回家。
I want to go home.
塞格医生：今天就够了。
DR. SEGAR: That's enough for today.
嗯，当然。我们会重新安排。
Uh, of course. We'll reschedule.
埃丝特，你没事吧？嗯,对。
Esther, you all right?Uh, yes.
嘿
Hey.
莫蒂西亚，帮我找甘纳，好吗？
Morticia, get Gunnar for me, would you?
你叫我什么？迈克，那是她。姐姐。
What did you call me?Mike, that's her. The sister.
噢，见鬼。
Oh, shit.
这是我的错。嗯，去找冈纳，波扎卢斯塔。
It's my bad. Um, get Gunnar, pozálujsta.
那是西班牙语还是什么？我不知道--
Is that Spanish or something? I don't--
嘿，我们走吧。
Hey, let's go.
你妹妹他妈的在旅行，伙计。
Your sister's a fuckin' trip, man.
说真的，伙计？我爸爸就在那里。
Seriously, dude? My dad is right there.
我不在乎。古纳：迈克！
I don't care.GUNNAR: Mike!
他妈的白痴。迈克：我就是我。
Fucking idiot.MIKE: I am what I am.
嘿，亲爱的，你没事吧？
Hey, honey, you okay?
呃，我的衣服坏了。艾伦：我给你买一个新的。
Uh, my dress is ruined.ALLEN: I'll buy you a new one.
我在想，呃，
I was thinking, uh,
我在想我们可以去演播室。
I was thinking we could go to the studio.
我很乐意。
I would love to.
如果我不知道的话，
If I didn't know any better,
我想你以前从没来过这里。
I'd think you'd never been in here before.
如此美丽。
So beautiful.
这盏灯是干什么用的？
What's the light for?
这盏灯是干什么用的？莉娜：嗯。
What's the light for?LEENA: Mm-hmm.
你不记得了？这就是你爸爸出名的原因。
You don't remember? It's what your papa's famous for.
隐马尔可夫模型。
Hmm.
在这里
Here.
按这个。
Press on this.
是的，我总是想把这么多东西放在一张画布上，
Yeah, I always tried to fit so much into one canvas,
你知道的？所以，我求助于一个隐藏层。
you know? So, I resorted to a-- a hidden layer.
什么都不是一回事，对吧？
Nothing is ever just one thing, right?
太酷了。
So cool.
你有一阵子没来过这里了。
You haven't been in here in a while.
不，我没有。
No, I haven't.
这是什么？
What's this one?
哦，不。
Oh, no.
我应该把它处理掉。
It's, uh, I should've gotten rid of this.
谁是谁？
Who-- who's-- who's that?
沉湎于过去是没有用的。
There's no use dwelling on the past.
你现在回家了。这才是最重要的，对吗？
You're home now. That's all that matters, right?
所以，我想我们可以擦掉一些画布，你知道吗？
So, I was thinking we could dust off some canvasses, you know?
看看结果如何。
See what comes of it.
我很乐意，是吗？
I would love to.Yeah?
嗯，你的毒药是什么？油画，水彩画？
Um, what's your poison? Oil, watercolors?
我都明白了，木炭？
I-- I got it all.Charcoal?
木炭可以
Charcoal? Okay.
挑一个物体，然后我们坐下来
Pick an object, and-- and we'll sit down
我们一起画。
and we'll-- we'll draw it together.
我想画你。
I want to draw you.
你想画我吗？嗯。
You want to draw me?Mm-hmm.
好的。
Yeah, okay.
这是第一次。
Well, this is a first.
你想要我怎么样？
How do you want me?
我能，我能做思想者。
I can-- I can do The Thinker.
你当时的样子。
The way you were when you were looking at that.
那不是我想住的地方了。
That's not a place I want to live anymore.
那里
There.
就这样。
Just like that.
你在那里学画画的？
You learned to paint while you were over there?
嗯。
Mm-hmm.
你只是画画，还是也画--
Would you just draw, or was it-- was it also--
不是你想的那样。
It wasn't what you think.
尽管发生了一切，它仍在发生
It's still happening, despite everything
这是怎么回事，艾伦？不，他不在那里。
that's going on. Allen? No, he won't be there.
你知道他对这些事情的感觉。
You know how he feels about these things.
那么，明天的晚会上见，好吗？
So, I'll see you at the gala tomorrow, then, okay?
这是为了一个好的理由。
It's for a good cause.
贝丝，带上你的支票簿和吉姆。
Beth, just bring your checkbook and Jim.
看在上帝的份上，这是为了儿科癌症。
It's for pediatric cancer, for Christ's sake.
好吧，这样更好。非常感谢。
Okay, that's better. Thank you.
我完了。
I'm finished.
已经嗯。
Already?Mm-hmm.
你喜欢吗？艾伦：我喜欢。
Do you like it?ALLEN: I love it.
太不可思议了。
It's-- it's incredible.
好的，30秒，好吗？
Okay, 30 seconds, all right?
然后我们会看看你能用油漆做什么。
And then we're gonna see what you can do with paint.
这是私人的。哦，对不起。
That's private.Oh, I'm sorry.
我看到你把它带回来了。
I-- I saw that you brought it back with you.
我觉得很特别。你不敲门吗？
I thought it was special.You don't knock?
我在找我的金表。
I was looking for, um, my gold watch.
没关系。我相信它会出现的。
I-- It's okay. I'm sure it'll turn up.
很抱歉
Sorry.
“以斯帖的财产。”
"Property of Esther."
“妈妈把我带到邪恶的地方。”
"Mummy took me to Wicked."
“妈妈”你好，妈妈。
"Mummy." Hello, Mummy.
谢谢你，妈妈。
Thank you, Mummy.
我知道，妈妈。
I know, Mummy.
妈咪
Mummy.
你不会相信埃丝特能做什么。
You're not gonna believe what Esther can do.
我们在演播室度过了下午。
We spent the afternoon in the studio.
她画了一幅我的肖像。
She drew a portrait of me.
她比我20多岁时更有天赋。
She's got more talent than I had when I was in my 20s.
这怎么可能？
How's that possible?
四年前，她还在画木棍。
Four years ago, she was still drawing stick figures.
容易的古纳：什么？
Easy.GUNNAR: What?
想想四年前你在哪里。
Think about where you were four years ago.
现在你是击剑冠军了。是的，只是，真是令人印象深刻。
Now you're a fencing champion.Yeah, just-- It's impressive.
隐马尔可夫模型。
Hmm.
也许你可以给我画一幅肖像。
Maybe you can make a portrait of me.
这很好吃，妈妈。
This is delicious, Mummy.
非常感谢。
Thank you.
有什么问题吗？
Is something wrong?
不，不，我只是--
No, no. I'm just--
你在等某人吗？
You expecting someone?
我想我会去。。。
I thought I'd pop in to...
看看谁来了。
Look who came for a visit.
哦，很抱歉打断你的晚餐。
Oh, I'm sorry to interrupt dinner.
这是一名警官
This is a police officer
你失踪时是谁帮助我们的。
who helped us when you went missing.
他是我的朋友。
He's a friend.
我只是来欢迎你回家埃丝特。
I just, uh, came to say welcome home, Esther.
非常感谢。
Thank you.
打扰一下。
Excuse me for a moment.
你应该知道，嗯，我们的儿童心理学家觉得
You should know, um, our child psychologist feels
埃丝特应该在他的范围内讲述她的故事--
Esther should tell her story within the confines of--
而不是和我这样的警察在一起。
And not with a cop like me.
别担心。我明白了。
Don't worry. I get it.
但埃丝特确实从我们的小镇上消失了，
But Esther did vanish from our little town,
这仍然是一个令人关切的问题。
and that remains a concern.
我需要知道是否还有危险。
I need to know if there's still a danger.
今天早上我和西格医生谈过了。
I spoke to Dr. Segar this morning.
这样合适吗？
Is that appropriate?
她告诉我她是开放的
She told me she's open
为了明天早上的小组讨论，
to group discussion tomorrow morning,
只是想看看是否一切都好。
just to see if everything's all right.
妈妈，你的晚会是明天。
Mummy, your gala is tomorrow.
那我们第二天再做。
We'll do it the following day, then.
这很重要。
It's important.
我是说，当然。如果有那么重要，我们会去的。
I mean, sure. If it's that important, we'll be there.
你忘了把杯子倒满。
You forgot to fill your glass.
欢迎回家，埃丝特。
Well, uh, welcome home, Esther.
你已经说过了。
You said that already.
埃丝特，没关系。她是对的。
Esther--Oh, it's okay. She's right.
我陪你出去。
I'll walk you out.
很抱歉你住在这里。
I'm sorry you live here.
是 啊
Yeah.
我想我会在这里呆一段时间。
I think I'll stay here for a while.
我想西格医生出了什么事。
I think something's going on with Dr. Segar.
在我们上次会面时，她似乎在暗示
She seemed to be implying in our last meeting
埃丝特在撒谎。
that Esther is lying.
那太疯狂了。
That's insane.
也许她需要看心理医生。
Maybe she needs to see a therapist.
我知道，对吧？
I know, right?
这是什么？
What-- what is this?
这是你的约会。
Your date.
你要来吗？是的，我当然会来。
You're coming?Yeah, of course I'm coming.
你是我的妻子。我可以帮你对付几个有钱人。
You're my wife. I can deal with a few rich pricks for you.
埃丝特呢？
And what about Esther?
嗯，甘纳来了。她会没事的，对吧？
Well, Gunnar's here. She'll be fine, right?
什么，你想让我呆在家里吗？
What, do you want me to stay home?
不，不。
No, no.
哦，你知道，自从我们把埃丝特救回来后，
Oh, you know, it seems like since we got Esther back,
我们也回来了。
we got us back, too.
我完全同意。
I couldn't agree more.
你需要多长时间穿衣服？
How long do you need to get dressed?
我可以快点，是吗？
I can be quick.Yeah?
我也可以很快。
I can be quick, too.
对不起，但它们很可爱。
I'm sorry, but they're cute.
我们把门关上。
Let's just close the door.
把门关上。
Just close the door.
什么不，不，不！
What? No. No, no, no!
哦，天哪。
Oh, my God.
你知道我花了多少钱买这件衣服吗？
Do you know how much I spent on this dress?
让我看看。哦，伙计。
Let me look.Oh, man.
我可以解决这个问题。
I can fix that.
用安全别针。对，或订书钉。
With a safety pin.Right, or staples.
史泰博会有用的。
Staples would work.
你有责任照顾你妹妹
You're responsible for looking after your sister
当我们离开的时候。我们相信你，好吗？
while we're gone. We're trusting you, okay?
是的，爸爸。我得到了它。
Yeah, Dad. I got it.
你看起来棒极了。
You look incredible.
我们出发了。
We're off.
可能要到午夜后才能回家，好吗？
Probably won't be home until after midnight, okay?
所以，不要让她熬夜太晚。
So, don't let her stay up too late.
你有钥匙吗？
You have the keys?
收到，嗯。
Copy that.Hmm.
你看起来不错。崔西亚：谢谢。
You look nice.TRICIA: Thanks.
祝你晚安，亲爱的。
Have a good night, honey.
再见，晚安。
Ciao.Night.
那我们该怎么办？
So what are we going to do?
我们
We?
♪ 我们有很多时间，感觉很好♪
♪ We got a lot of time And it sure feels right ♪
♪ '因为你把手伸进了口袋♪
♪ 'Cause you reached In your pocket ♪
♪ 你必须赢一点♪
♪ You've got to win a little ♪
♪ 失去一点
♪ Lose a little
♪ 总是有点忧郁♪
♪ And always have The blues a little ♪
哦，这是，哦，见鬼，伙计们。我很抱歉。
Oh, it's-- Oh, shit, guys. I'm sorry.
我抓得太久了。
I was holding onto it for too long.
可以那么，贡纳，
Okay. So, Gunnar,
你妹妹和你记忆中的不同吗？
is your sister different than you remember?
迈克：你觉得怎么样？
I mean--MIKE: What do you think?
她去过东欧的性集中营。
She's been at some Eastern European sex gulag.
迈克。
Mike.
但是，嗯，是的。不，她，呃，她不一样，好吧。
But, uh, yeah. No, she, uh, she's different, all right.
她现在有口音了。
She's got an accent now.
她穿着像莉齐·波登。
And she dresses like Lizzie Borden.
真他妈的奇怪。
It's so fucking weird.
莉齐·波登是谁？
Who's Lizzie Borden?
♪ 沙拉拉。。。
♪ Sha la-la la...
一个疯狂的小妞用斧头杀了她的父母。
Some crazy chick who killed her parents with an axe.
呃，嘿，埃丝特，
Uh, hey, Esther,
你为什么不去看电影什么的？
why don't you, uh, go watch a movie or something?
不
No.
埃丝特，这不是你的戏。
Esther, this isn't your scene.
去看电影。去他妈的。
Go watch a movie.Go fuck yourself.
嘿，甘纳，你知道吗？我喜欢她。
Hey, Gunnar, you know what? I like her.
哦
Oh.
去
Go.
无论如何，干杯！女孩2：干杯。
Anyway, cheers!GIRL 2: Cheers.
是 啊我他妈的要为此干杯。
Yeah. I'll fucking drink to that.
嗯，我们在说什么？
Um, what we were talking about?
那是谁？
Who's that?
傍晚
Evening.
嘿，我父母不在这里。他们在妈妈的晚会上。
Hey, my parents aren't here. They're at Mom's gala.
真倒霉甘纳：是的。
Just my luck.GUNNAR: Yeah.
开派对？
Having a party?
不，只是几个朋友。
No, it's just a few friends.
闻闻街上的杂草。
Smell the weed from the street.
什么嗯，我不知道--
What? Um, I don't know--
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know what you're talking about.
听着，这里什么都没发生，好吗？
Um, look, nothing's going on here, okay?
那我为什么不直接告诉我父母
So um, why don't I just tell my parents
你来过我们可以忘掉这一切。
that you stopped by, and we can just forget all about this.
凉的
Cool?
很酷，很好。
Cool.Good.
你介意我去洗手间吗？
You mind if I hit the restroom before I go?
是的，随便。是的，当然。
Yeah, whatever. Yeah, sure.
那是一场爆炸。
That was a blast.
难怪那些紧张的百万富翁排队
No wonder those uptight millionaires line up
给基金会钱。
to give the foundation money.
哦，不，是酒。
Oh, no. It's the booze.
这不是酒，亲爱的。
It's not the booze, hon.
是主人。
It's the host.
你让人们发挥出最好的一面。
You bring the best out of people.
哦。
Aw.
我只希望这房子还屹立着。
I just hope the house is still standing.
啊。
Ugh.
我是说，当我16岁的时候，我几乎。。。
I mean, when I was 16, I-- I nearly...
…我差点把房子烧了。
...I nearly burnt the house down.
不，甘纳不会那样做的。
No, Gunnar would never do that.
谁说我说的是甘纳？
Who says I'm talking about Gunnar?
埃丝特，我们到家了。
Esther, we're home.
埃丝特？
Esther?
“萨恩学院？”
"Saarne Institute?"
埃丝特？
Esther?
如果你不是埃丝特，你到底是谁？
If you're not Esther, who the hell are you?
你怎么知道我不是埃丝特？
How did you know that I'm not Esther?
她自己的母亲甚至不知道。
Her own mother doesn't even know.
是的，孩子，她喜欢。
Yeah, kid, she does.
该死的。
Damn it.
妈咪
Mummy?
你他妈的在看什么？
The fuck are you looking at?
所以，让我直说吧。
So, let me get this straight.
你是个成年女人还是通缉犯？
You're a grown-ass woman and a wanted criminal?
这简直是一团糟。
That is beyond fucked up.
顺便说一句，这就是我所做的一切。
This is all I ever do anymore, by the way.
收拾我的孩子。
Clean up after my kids.
别担心。妈妈会处理好的。
Don't worry about it. Mommy'll take care of it.
妈妈会照顾好一切。
Mommy takes care of everything.
当Gunnar告诉我Donnan来了，
When Gunnar told me Donnan came to the house,
我知道我会在这里找到你。
I knew I'd find you here.
你本可以抢了我们的钱然后消失
You could have robbed us blind and disappeared
第二次你有机会，但你没有。
the second you had a chance, but you didn't.
为什么？
Why is that?
你想的更大，对吗？扮演角色，操纵我们，
You're thinking bigger, right? Play the part, manipulate us,
一年后，我们遇到了一些悲惨的事故。
and a year from now we meet with some tragic accident.
我暖和了吗？
Am I getting warm?
让我走。你再也见不到我了。
Let me go. You'll never see me again.
这正是我害怕的。
That's exactly what I'm afraid of.
我们不能让埃丝特消失两次，对吗？
We can't have Esther disappear twice now, can we?
她没有消失。
She didn't disappear.
我无法为她做任何事，
There was nothing that I could do for her,
太晚了。
it was too late.
甘纳，他对她总是太粗暴了。
Gunnar, he was always way too rough with her.
那天晚上他做得太过分了。我该怎么办？
That night he just went too far. What was I supposed to do?
把我剩下的唯一的孩子交出来
Hand over the only child I had left over some
兄弟姐妹的胡说八道太过分了？
sibling bullshit that went too far?
我全心全意地爱我的女儿，
I loved my daughter with all my heart,
但是一个母亲保护她的家庭，不管发生什么，
but a mother protects her family, no matter what,
如果你认为…我会让一些
and if you think... ...that I'm going to let some
精神侏儒摧毁我建造的。。。
psycho dwarf destroy what I have built...
你错了。
you're mistaken.
这家人是他妈的五月花号来的
This family came over on the fucking Mayflower
建立了这个国家。我们很重要。艾伦很重要。
and built this country. We matter. Allen matters.
当他得知以斯帖还活着的消息时，
When he got the news Esther was alive,
他脸上的幸福，我必须让这件事成功。
the happiness on his face, I had to make this work.
艾伦不知道埃丝特怎么了。
Allen doesn't know what happened to Esther.
你要帮我确保他永远不会这样做。
And you are gonna help me make sure that he never does.
只有一件事比孩子的死更糟糕，
There's only one thing worse than the death of a child,
那是一个失踪的孩子。
and that is a child who is missing.
埃丝特的失踪改变了艾伦，
Esther's disappearance changed Allen,
改变了他是谁，他应该是谁，
changed who he was, who he is supposed to be,
但你就是答案。
but you are the answer.
你和我有机会扭转局面
You and I have a chance to turn this mess
成为互惠的安排。
into a mutually beneficial arrangement.
埃丝特在下面，不是吗？
Esther's down there, isn't she?
你他妈的别说她的名字。
Don't you fucking say her name.
可以
Okay.
你骗进了我家。
You conned your way into my family.
你选择了这个角色，
You chose this role,
现在你他妈的要玩了。
and now you're gonna fucking play it.
所以，你现在可以成为以斯帖，
So, you can be Esther for now,
过着一种任何人都会杀掉的生活，
and live a life that anyone would kill to have,
或者你为此承担责任
or you take the fall for this
带着手铐被运回爱沙尼亚。
and get shipped back to Estonia in handcuffs.
你怎么说？
What do you say?
对不起，我吓到你了。艾伦：对不起。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry I scared you.ALLEN: I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我们不应该让你一个人呆着。
We should have never left you alone.
怎么搞的？她从自行车上摔了下来。
What happened?She fell off her bike.
我在路边发现了她。
I found her by the side of the road.
亲爱的，你骑自行车干什么？
Honey, what are you doing on a bike?
过来，让我们暖和起来。
Come here, let's-- let's get warm.
妈妈，我很抱歉，停下来。
Mom, I'm so sorry.Stop.
卧槽？是 啊
What the fuck?Yeah.
那么这意味着什么呢？
So what does this mean?
这意味着她不是孩子。
Well, it means she's not a kid.
她是个成熟的女人，我们不能低估她。
She is a grown woman and we cannot underestimate her.
不，她不止于此，妈妈。
No, she's more than that, Mother.
她是一个住在我们他妈的房子里的精神病患者。
She's a psychopath living in our fucking house.
所以我们只能和这个人一起生活？
So we just have to live with this person?
我没这么说。那么，我们能不能，你知道吗？
I didn't say that.So then, can we just, you know?
让它看起来像一场意外。
Make it look like an accident.
太早了。我们需要考虑这一点。
It's too soon. We need to think about this.
所以她现在是我们的主人？
So she just owns us now?
不，不，她和我们一样有很多损失。
No, no, she has just as much to lose as we do.
听着，我们俩都没想到会这样。
Look, neither of us were expecting this.
所以，现在我们只是看着她，
So, for now we just keep an eye on her,
时机成熟时，我们就结束它。
and when the time is right, we'll end it.
这太疯狂了，即使对我们来说也是如此。
This is insane, even for us.
好吧，看到了吗？会着火的。
Okay, see that? It's gonna fire.
嗯。把它拉回来。就这样。
Uh-huh.Pull it back. Just like that.
然后你得到弓，把它翻进去，滑动它。
And you get the bow, flip it in, slide it.
看到这个了吗？你在看吗？是 啊
See this? Are you watching?Yeah.
是的，你呢--
Yeah, and you--
美好的
Nice!
你看到了吗？艾伦：是的，是的。
You see that?ALLEN: Yeah, yeah.
这就是我要说的。
That's what I'm talking about.
我们今天要和Segar博士会面。
Our meeting with Dr. Segar is today.
如果你不说话，我们就不会有问题
A problem we wouldn't have if you hadn't talked
给鹦鹉。
to the parrot.
悉尼是一只金刚鹦鹉。
Sydney was a macaw.Oh.
所有金刚鹦鹉，
All macaws are parrots,
但不是所有他妈的鹦鹉都是金刚鹦鹉。
but not all fucking parrots are macaws.
我们该怎么办？
What are we gonna do about that?
哦，我们让她相信。在一起
Oh, we make her believe. Together.
西格尔博士：我们的目标之一是帮助埃丝特适应环境
DR. SEGAR: One of our goals here is helping Esther acclimate
回到家庭生活中。
back into life within the family unit.
其中一部分是回忆你共同的历史。
Part of that is remembering your shared history.
你们在一起的时光，你们以前一起做的有趣的事情。
Moments you had, the fun things you did together before.
奥尔布赖特先生，什么是有意义的记忆
Mr. Albright, what's a memory that means a lot
给你和埃丝特？
to you and to Esther?
哦，天哪，太多了。
Oh, God, there are so many.
巴黎有个圣诞节。
Um, there was Christmas in Paris.
托斯卡纳的夏天。
The summer in Tuscany.
黄石公园。艾伦：是的，就在上面。
Yellowstone.ALLEN: Yeah, that's up there.
我六岁。
I was six.
我们看到熊和一只花栗鼠偷走了我的三明治。
We saw bears and a-- a chipmunk stole my sandwich.
哦，天哪。有那么多花栗鼠。
Oh, my God. There were so many chipmunks.
还有什么，埃丝特？要具体。
What else, Esther? Be specific.
我们住在麋鹿岭牧场，骑马。
We stayed at Elk Ridge Ranch and rode horses.
我的是一匹名叫努吉特的小马
Mine was a pony named Nugget
爸爸的马叫舒展，
and Daddy's horse was called Stretch,
这一次，当斯泰奇俯身吃草时，
and this one time when Stretch leaned down to eat grass,
爸爸一头栽在地上。
Daddy fell right over his head onto the ground.
他满脸都是污垢。甚至在他的牙齿里！
He had dirt all over his face. It was even in his teeth!
我不敢相信你在讲这个故事。
I can't believe you're telling this story.
哦，天哪。它在你的牙齿里好几天了。
Oh, my God. It was in your teeth for days.
总之，埃丝特展现了健康的人生观，
In summary, Esther exhibits a healthy outlook on life,
尤其是重新进入这个家庭单元。
especially re-entering into this family unit.
她功能很强，
She is highly functioning,
情感上很好。
emotionally well.
仅此而已。
That is all.
今天有人过来
There are people coming over today
只是想见你。
just to see you.
他们是我们认识埃丝特的朋友。
They're friends of ours who knew Esther.
别再怒目而视了，好吗？
So enough with the glowering, okay?
埃丝特是一位女士。
Esther is a lady.
隐马尔可夫模型。
Hmm.
我想我得做点破坏。
I think I'm gonna have to do some damage.
可以
Okay.
我认为我们做得很好。
Think we did good.
每个人都希望埃丝特破产。
Everyone expects Esther to be broken.
他们真正想要的是一个幸福的结局。
What they really want is a happy ending.
我们要假装
We are gonna pretend
那粉红色是你最喜欢的颜色。
that pink is your favorite color.
噢，天鹅绒。
Ooh, velvet.
秘密是给他们一个他们想相信的故事。
The secret is to give them a story they want to believe.
这是我最喜欢的。
This one is my favorite.
你最喜欢什么颜色？粉红色
What's your favorite color? Pink.
非常非常好。
Very, very good.
现在，你说你会画画。你还能做什么？
Now, you say you can paint. What else can you do?
我非常想念我的家人。
I missed my family very much.
回来真是太好了。
It's lovely to be back.
你现在有什么计划，小姐？
And what are your plans now, young lady?
我的计划是什么，妈妈？
What are my plans, Mummy?
绝对没有。
Absolutely nothing.
我不会让你离开我的视线。
I'm not letting you out of my sight.
哦。
Aw.
让我直说吧。。。
So let me get this straight...
你30岁了？
you're 30?
请离开我的房间。
Get out of my room now, please.
这不是你的房间。这是我死去姐姐的房间。
It's not your room. It's my dead sister's room.
你不是她，你永远也不会。
You're not her and you never will be.
清楚吗？滚开。
Is that perfectly clear?Fuck off.
小心你的嘴，怪物。
Watch your mouth, freak.
我很高兴现在一切都公开了，
You know, I'm glad everything's out in the open now,
因为我受够了假装你属于这里。
'cause I'm done pretending like you belong here.
你没有。
You don't.
这是我的房子，我的家人，永远不会是你的。
This is my house, my family, it'll never be yours.
只要你在这个屋檐下，
As long as you're under this roof,
你和我会有一个谅解。
you and I will have an understanding.
这就是它。
Here's what it is.
我他妈的拥有你。
I fucking own you.
再这样做，我就杀了你，就像我杀了埃丝特一样。
Do that again and I'll kill you like I killed Esther.
我打了一个电话，
One call from me,
你又回到了古拉格。
and you're right back in that gulag.
你也会下去的。
You'd go down, too.
为什么，因为非法移民，逃犯，
Why, because of what the illegal immigrant, fugitive,
精神病人说什么？
mental patient said?
祝你好运。
Good luck with that.
这是美国。
This is America.
像我这样的人很重要，
People like me matter,
如果你不是埃丝特，
and if you're not Esther,
那只是意味着埃丝特又失踪了。
that just means Esther's missing again.
妈妈对此有问题。
Mom has a problem with that.
我不。
I don't.
再见，怪胎。
See you later, freak.
你今晚会睡得像个该死的婴儿。
You are gonna sleep like a fucking baby tonight.
我用迷迭香和肉酱做了烤羊肉。
I made roast lamb with rosemary and tapenade.
我知道埃丝特不喜欢，
And I know Esther doesn't like it,
所以我做了你最喜欢的。
so I made your favorite.
噢，就像过去一样。
Aw, just like the old days.
我真的很兴奋能去
I'm really excited about going
明天进城。
into the city tomorrow.
我要向画廊展示我一直在做的。
I'm gonna show the gallery what I've been working on.
听起来很棒。
That sounds wonderful.
好吧，这都是你的功劳。
Well, it's all thanks to you.Oh.
我重新发现了做我喜欢的事情的快乐。
I rediscovered the joy I once felt doing what I love.
我觉得自己又像个孩子了。你想来吗？
I feel like a kid again. You want to come?
我很乐意！
I would love to!
哦，埃丝特和我已经有计划了。
Oh, Esther and I already have plans.
哦有什么计划？
Oh.What plans?
这是一个惊喜。
It's a surprise.
好吧，下次吧。
Okay, well, another time then.
爸爸，你又在画画真是太好了。
It's great that you're painting again, Dad.
嗯，是的。
Well, yeah.
可以原谅我吗？
May I be excused?
哦，别忘了你的--
Oh, don't forget your--
你可以在楼上吃。没关系。
You can eat upstairs. It's okay.
亲爱的，嘿，怎么了？
Honey, hey, what's wrong?
爸爸，她很好。
Dad, she's fine.
给她点空间。她很好。
Just give her some space. She's fine.
是的，她可能因为弹钢琴累了。
Yeah, she's probably tired from all that piano playing.
我可以进来吗？嗯。
Can I come in?Mm-hmm.
你没事吧？下面发生了什么？
Are you okay? What happened down there?
一、 我不太喜欢妈妈做的菜。
I, uh, I don't really like Mummy's cooking.
你能保守秘密吗？
Well, can you keep a secret?
我也不疯狂。
I'm not crazy about it either.
听着晚上是我最喜欢画画的时间。
Well, listen, um, nighttime's my favorite time to paint.
你想和我一起去吗？
You-- you want to come join me?
是的，我很乐意。艾伦：我们楼下见。
Yes, I would love to.ALLEN: I'll see you downstairs.
这是一个如此巨大的空间。我很高兴你喜欢它。
This is a such a great space.I'm glad you like it.
每个艺术家都需要一个空间来释放他们内心的怪癖。
Every artist needs a space to let their inner weirdo out.
我们可以看到美丽和激情
We get to see beauty and passion
其他人甚至不知道去哪里看。
where others don't even know to look.
我真的很喜欢。
I really like that.
油漆太多了。
So much paint.
是的，我是个邋遢的画家。
Yeah, I'm a messy painter.
这让你妈妈发疯。
Drives your mother crazy.
我想我今晚已经完了。
I think I'm-- I think I'm done for the night.
把灯关掉就行了。
Just turn the lights off.
祝你晚安。
Have a good night.
看起来你们俩玩得很开心。
Looks like you two had fun.
他是对的，你很有天赋。
He's right, you are talented.
他很了不起，不是吗？
He is something, isn't he?
你以为他会想要你，难道你完全是在妄想吗？
Are you so utterly delusional to think that he would want you?
“令人惊讶的是，我不是你的女儿，
"Surprise, I'm not your daughter,
我是个变种骗子。“
I'm a mutant grifter."
他会像我猜想的大多数男人一样被你排斥。
He would be as repulsed by you as I suspect most men are.
好吧，请原谅，
Well, if you'll excuse me,
我要上楼去操我丈夫。
I'm gonna go upstairs and fuck my husband.
自从你回来后，他真的是个新人。
He really is a new man since you came back.
谢谢。
Thanks for that.
嘿，你。
Hey, you.
我想埃丝特对不来真的很失望
I think Esther's really bummed about not coming
和我一起去画廊。
to the gallery with me.
听着，我喜欢你和埃丝特
Listen, I love that you and Esther
有共同之处。我只是--
have painting in common. I just--
我和她没有这样的关系。
I don't have anything like that with her.
我希望能和她一起度过这一天
I was hoping that I could spend the day with her
也许我们可以找点东西分享。
and maybe we could find something to share.
另外，集中注意力对你有好处，对吗？
Plus, it would be good for you to be focused, right?
如果萨尔喜欢他看到的东西，
I mean, if Sal likes what he sees,
然后也许你可以去看一场表演，然后回到那里。
then maybe you get a show and get back out there.
是的，好的。我们没有受伤，是吗？
Yeah, okay. We're not hurting, are we?
不，不，一点也不。
No, no. Not at all.
你是一位伟大的画家。
You are a great painter.
人们错过了看你的作品。
People miss seeing your work.
非常感谢。
Thank you.
那是培根吗？
Is that bacon?
这是天堂。
It's heaven.
早上好，爸爸。绉纱？
Good morning, Daddy. Crepe?
是的，请。有什么你不能做的吗？
Yes, please. Is there anything you can't do?
妈咪
Mummy?
哦，不，谢谢。我要像往常一样--
Oh, no, thanks. I'm gonna make my usual--
奶昔？
Smoothie?
希腊酸奶、羽衣甘蓝、亚麻籽和柠檬汁。
Greek yogurt, kale, flax seeds, and lemon juice.
就是你喜欢的方式。
Just the way you like it.
试试看。
Try it.
我真的没那么饿。
I'm not really that hungry.
我会的。在这里
I'll-- I'll have it. Here.
不，这是专为妈妈准备的。
No, this is special just for mummy.
我为你做的。
I made it for you.
哦，亲爱的，你真好，
Oh, sweetie, that's so nice of you,
但我更喜欢自己做。
but I prefer to make my own.
特里西亚，来吧，试试看。
Tricia, come on. Try it.
好的
Good.
嗯，很好吃。
Mm, delicious.
非常感谢。
Thank you.
特里西亚，你没事吧？我很好。
Tricia, you okay?I'm good.
是 啊
Yeah?
我知道你想和我一起去，
I know you wanted to come with me,
但我认为这一天对你来说真的很好
but I think it'll be really good for you to spend the day
和你妈妈在一起。不过我想给你看点东西。
with your mom. I wanted to show you something, though.
在这里
Here.
在中间的那个。
It's the one in the center.
伍德利学院的院长是我的朋友。
Dean at Woodley is a friend of mine.
伍德利是全国最好的艺术学校。
Woodley is the best art school in the country.
你真是太可怕了，埃丝特。我能给他们看看吗？
You're scary good, Esther. Can I show it to 'em?
我会喜欢的。非常感谢。
I would love it. Thank you.
你能把这个带到站台上吗？
Can you bring this up to the platform?
我要给爸爸妈妈买些咖啡。
I'm just gonna get some coffees for Mom and Dad.
嗯。
Mm-hmm.
好吧，我们在上面见。
All right, I'll see you up there.
耶稣基督！小心你要去哪里，孩子！
Jesus Christ! Watch where you're going, kid!
她属于你吗？特里西亚：是的，她有。
Does she belong to you?TRICIA: Yes, she does.
怎么搞的？哦，没什么。很好。
What happened?Oh, nothing. It's fine.
埃丝特绊倒了。艾伦：对不起，这花了很长时间。
Esther tripped.ALLEN: Sorry, it took forever.
不，不！把他们打死，好吗？是 啊
No, no! Knock 'em dead, okay?Yeah.
爸爸，带我一起去！
Daddy, take me with you!
噢，亲爱的，我希望如此。下一次
Oh, honey, I wish. Next time.
你会错过火车的。好吧，再见，亲爱的。
You're gonna miss your train.All right, see you later, honey.
再见。
Ciao.
别紧张，妈妈。
Easy, Mom.
你以为你他妈能杀了我？
You think you can fucking kill me?
拿着这个。
Take this.
味道像他妈的垃圾。
Tastes like fucking garbage.
我们的安排结束了。你他妈的死了。
Our arrangement is over. You're fucking dead.
嘿
Hey!
妈妈妈妈
Mom! Mom!
性交！婊子！
Fuck! Bitch!
打开该死的门。埃丝特！
Open the God damn door. Esther!
亲爱的，来吧。
Sweetie, come on.
你敢！
Don't you dare!
♪ 只是一个周六晚上的钢铁城女孩♪
♪ Just a steel town girl On a Saturday night ♪
♪ 寻找她生命中的战斗♪
♪ Lookin' for The fight of her life ♪
♪ 在实时世界中，根本没有人看到她♪
♪ In the real-time world No one sees her at all ♪
♪ 他们都说她疯了♪
♪ They all say she's crazy ♪
♪ 它可以像刀一样割你
♪ It can cut you like a knife
♪ 如果礼物变成了火♪
♪ If the gift becomes the fire ♪
♪ 在意志和未来之间的电线上♪
♪ On a wire between Will and what will be ♪
♪ 她是个疯子，地板上的疯子♪
♪ She's a maniac Maniac on the floor ♪
♪ 她跳舞的样子前所未有♪
♪ And she's dancing Like she's never danced before ♪
♪ 她是个疯子，地板上的疯子♪
♪ She's a maniac Maniac on the floor ♪
♪ 她跳舞的样子。。。
♪ And she's dancing like...
我很抱歉。我开得太快了吗？
I'm sorry. Was I driving too fast?
你一定是埃丝特。
You must be Esther.
我需要去医院。
I need to go to the hospital.
你很好。
You're fine.
感觉我被他妈的捅了1000刀。
Feels like I'm being stabbed a 1,000 fucking times.
利希警官。甘纳：噢，我的上帝。
Officer Leahy.GUNNAR: Oh, my God.
你能安静两秒钟吗？
Can you just be quiet for, like, two seconds?
什么莉希：我们找到埃丝特了。
What?LEAHY: We've located Esther.
你做到了吗？莉希：我要带她回家。
You did?LEAHY: I'm bringing her home.
哦
Oh.
哦，我也通知了艾伦。
Oh, and I've informed Allen as well.
好的，再见。性交！
Okay, bye. Fuck!
你没事。你没事。
You're okay. You're okay.
非常感谢。
Thank you so much.
哦，天哪。哦
Oh, my goodness. Oh.
非常感谢。
Thank you so much.
埃丝特回来后表现得很不稳定。
Esther's behavior has been so erratic since she got back.
老实说，这真的很难。
To be honest, it's been really hard.
我的意思是，有不断的谎言和这些愤怒的爆发。
I mean, there's constant lying and these outbursts of anger.
有时她甚至开玩笑说自己受伤了
Sometimes she even jokes about hurting herself
我觉得她不是在开玩笑。
and I don't think she's really joking.
你让她接受治疗？对,对。
You have her in therapy?Yes, yes.
看看谁回来了。
Look who's back.
起床我们正在这样做。现在
Get up. We're doing this. Now.
是时候了。
Well, it's about goddamn time.
性交。
Fuck.
我和你无瓜葛了。
I am done with you.
没有什么值得你呆在这房子里。
Nothing is worth having you in this house.
你的自杀会让爸爸心碎，
Your suicide is gonna break Daddy's heart,
但他会克服的。
but he'll get over it.
啊。
Ugh.
去死吧，你这个怪胎！
Just die, you freak!
她在哪里？
Where is she?
我不是有意的。
I-- I-- I didn't mean to.
哦，太棒了。
Oh, that's just brilliant.
事情就这样发生了。
It just happened.
特里西亚。嗨，亲爱的。
Tricia.Hi, honey.
警察刚打电话给我。
The police just called me.
哦，我知道。对不起。这是我的错。
Oh, I know. I'm-- I'm sorry. It was my fault.
埃丝特在商店闲逛，
Esther wandered off at the store,
我只是，我惊慌失措，
and I just-- I panicked,
但我打电话给莱希警官…妈妈。
but I called Officer Leahy...Mom.
…他们找到了她。
...and they found her.
哦，很好，妈妈。
Oh, good.Mom.
我在火车上，什么？
Well, I'm on the train.What?
她，等等。
She's--Hold on.
我要回家了。
I'm-- I'm coming back home.
我会。。。
I'll be...
下楼把它做完。
Go downstairs and finish it.
什么下楼把它做完。
What?Go downstairs and finish it.
特里西亚，你还在吗？
Tricia, are you still there?
特里西亚，一切都好吗？
Tricia, is everything okay?
特里西亚，我现在要回家了。
Tricia, I-- I'm coming home now.
什么艾伦：我要回家了。
What?ALLEN: I'm coming home.
你和萨尔的会面怎么样？
What about your meeting with Sal?
算了吧。
Forget about that.
不，亲爱的。我发誓。一切都很好。
No, sweetie. I swear. Everything is fine.
埃丝特来了一切都很好。
Esther is here, all is well.
听着，我快到城里的火车站了。
Look, I'm almost at the station in town.
好吧，你能坐出租车回家吗？
Okay, well, can you please take a cab home?
因为我真的忙得不可开交。
Because I really have my hands full here.
噢，去他妈的。
Ow, fuck it.
给你。
There you are.
埃丝特。
Esther.
出来吧，埃丝特
Come on out, Esther
或者你他妈的叫什么名字。
or whatever the fuck your name is.
你知道，它不必是这样的。
You know, it doesn't have to be like this.
真的吗，贡纳？
Really, Gunnar?
我相信我们能想出办法。
I'm sure we could figure something out.
你真的相信吗？
You really believe that?
真的
Honestly?
不
No.
我也是。
Me neither.
倒霉。
Shit.
甘纳？
Gunnar?
不
No.
No!
你做了什么？你做了什么？
What have you done? What have you done?
你拿走了一切。
You've taken everything.
艾伦永远不会是你的，
Allen will never be yours,
但我可以我向你保证他会知道你是谁。
but I can I promise you this, he will know who you are.
操纵我们悲伤的畸形人，
The deformed freak who manipulated our grief,
杀了我儿子，还想杀了我。
murdered my son, and tried to kill me.
直到我做了该做的事。
Until I did what had to be done.
打电话给消防局！
Call the fire department!
甘纳！
Gunnar!
等一下，我来了！
Hold on, I'm coming!
帮助莉娜：爸爸，妈妈想伤害我！
Help!LEENA: Daddy, Mommy tried to hurt me!
艾伦！请帮忙！
Allen! Please help!
艾伦！艾伦：别松手！
Allen!ALLEN: Don't let go!
我坚持不了多久了。
I can't hold on much longer.
我失去控制了！
I'm losing my grip!
爸爸，救命！艾伦：亲爱的，等等，等等！
Daddy, help!ALLEN: Honey, hang on. Hang on!
我来了。
I'm coming.
她不是埃丝特！她是个成熟的女人！
She is not Esther! She is a grown woman!
她在撒谎！什么
She's lying!What?
她骗了我们！妈妈在撒谎！
She tricked us!Mummy's lying!
把手给我！不，爸爸！请帮帮我！
Give me your hand!No, Daddy! Please help me!
特里西亚！
Tricia!
卧槽？我这么做是为了你。对我们来说。
What the fuck?I did this for you. For us.
所以我们可以在一起。艾伦，我爱你。
So we could be together. Allen, I love you.
你他妈的是谁？你是个怪物！
Who the fuck are you? You're a monster!
艾伦！
Allen!
♪ 你得付出一点
♪ You've gotta give a little
♪ 吃一点
♪ Take a little
♪ 让你可怜的心破碎一点♪
♪ And let your poor heart Break a little ♪
♪ 这就是爱的故事，这是爱的荣耀♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
♪ 你得笑一笑
♪ You've gotta laugh a little
♪ 哭一点♪
♪ Cry a little ♪
♪ 在云层翻滚之前♪
♪ Before the clouds Roll by a little ♪
♪ 这就是爱的故事，这是爱的荣耀♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
♪ 只要有你们两个♪
♪ As long as there's The two of you ♪
♪ 你拥有这个世界和它所有的魅力♪
♪ You've got the world And all its charms ♪
♪ 当你的世界结束的时候♪
♪ And when the world is Through with you ♪
♪ 你们有彼此的手臂
♪ You've got each other's arms
♪ 你得赢一点♪
♪ You've gotta win a little ♪
♪ 失去一点
♪ Lose a little
♪ 总是有点忧郁♪
♪ And always have The blues a little ♪
♪ 这就是爱的故事，这是爱的荣耀♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
塞格医生：大火夺走了埃丝特的一切。
DR. SEGAR: Fire took everything from Esther.
她的家，她的家人。
Her home, her family.
整个情况是如此悲惨。
The whole situation is so tragic.
太可怕了。
It's horrifying.
我知道。
I know.
好像埃丝特还没经历够似的。
As if Esther hasn't been through enough already.
被绑架，现在成了孤儿，没有家人收留她？
Abducted and now an orphan with no family to take her in?
现在会发生什么？
What will happen now?
SEGAR博士：我已经联系了一家声誉良好的收养机构。
DR. SEGAR: I've reached out to a reputable adoption agency.
我相信我们会找到一个家
I'm confident we'll find a home
在那里埃丝特可以得到她应得的支持和爱。
where Esther can get the support and love she deserves.
毕竟，谁不想收养她？
After all, who wouldn't want to adopt her?